{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What programming language did I write the first line of code in?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Python", "C++", "Java"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which university did I graduate from?",
      "options": ["Economics", "Math", "Philosophy", "English language"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What year did I have my first programming experience?",
      "options": [2021, 2018, 2022, 2024],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following hobbies is my favorite?",
      "options": [
        "Playing football",
        "Writing",
        "Reading books",
        "Playing a guitar"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country do I want to visit the most?",
      "options": ["China", "USA", "Russia", "Italy"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In which of the following technologies did I have experience?",
      "options": ["Vue", "Angular", "Laravel", "Rust"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which field am I interested in, besides front-end web development?",
      "options": [
        "Artificial intelligence (AI)",
        "Cybersecurity",
        "Back-end",
        "Data analysis"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is my favorite movie?",
      "options": [
        "Life is beautiful",
        "Pulp fiction",
        "Shawshank redemption",
        "Taxi driver"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sport did I play as a child?",
      "options": ["Basketball", "Swimming", "Football", "Tennis"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which celebrity would I like to meet and talk to?",
      "options": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Johnny Dep",
        "Novak Djokovic",
        "Michael Jordan"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
